<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="storyLine">
        <item>Jake Sully lives with his newfound family formed on the extrasolar moon Pandora. Once a familiar threat returns to finish what was previously started, Jake must work with Neytiri and the army of the Na\'vi race to protect their home.</item>
        <item>Set in the American West of 1876, \'R.I.P.D.2: Rise of the Damed\' is a spiritual (pardon the pun) sequel to 2013\'s \'R.I.P.D.\' Sheriff Roy Pulsipher isn\'t too thrilled about finding himself dead after a shoot out with a notorious outlaw gang, but he does get a second chance to return to earth after being recruited by the R.I.P.D. (Rest In Peace Department.). But avenging his own murder may have to take a back seat to saving the world when a gateway to hell is opened in the old mining town of Red Creek threatening not only the locals... but all of humanity itself.</item>
        <item>Queen Ramonda, Shuri, M\'Baku, Okoye and the Dora Milaje fight to protect the kingdom of Wakanda from intervening world powers in the wake of King T\'Challa\'s death. As the Wakandans strive to embrace their next chapter, the heroes must band together with the help of War Dog Nakia and Everett Ross and forge a new path for their nation.</item>
        <item>Reawakening after 5000 years, Black Adam becomes the world\'s ruthless protector: an anti-villain to take on the likes of Superman and Wonder Woman. Now in the 21st-Century, Black Adam must face off against the Justice Society of America and its heroes: Doctor Fate, Hawkman, Atom Smasher and Cyclone. The fate of the world hangs in the balance.</item>
        <item>Thor\'s retirement is interrupted by a galactic killer known as Gorr the God Butcher, who seeks the extinction of the gods. To combat the threat, Thor enlists the help of King Valkyrie, Korg and ex-girlfriend Jane Foster, who - to Thor\'s surprise - inexplicably wields his magical hammer, Mjolnir, as the Mighty Thor. Together, they embark upon a harrowing cosmic adventure to uncover the mystery of the God Butcher\'s vengeance and stop him before it\'s too late.</item>
        <item>In the heart of the 1970s, amidst a flurry of feathered hair and flared jeans, Gru (Steve Carell) is growing up in the suburbs. A fanboy of a supervillain supergroup known as the Vicious 6, Gru hatches a plan to become evil enough to join them. Luckily, he gets some mayhem-making back-up from his loyal followers, the Minions. Together, Kevin, Stuart, Bob, and Otto - a new Minion sporting braces and a desperate need to please - deploy their skills as they and Gru build their first lair, experiment with their first weapons, and pull off their first missions. When the Vicious 6 oust their leader, legendary fighter Wild Knuckles (Alan Arkin), Gru interviews to become their newest member. It doesn\'t go well (to say the least), and only gets worse after Gru outsmarts them and suddenly finds himself the mortal enemy of the apex of evil. On the run, Gru will turn to an unlikely source for guidance, Wild Knuckles, and discover that even bad guys need a little help from their friends.</item>
        <item>The world\'s deadliest assassin and New York\'s biggest screw-up are mistaken for each other at an Airbnb rental.</item>
        <item>After surviving the destruction of Isla Nubla, Owen Grady and Claire Dearing took in young Maisie Lockwood. They\'ve been living under the radar to protect Maisie, but she feels like a prisoner. When Maisie goes missing, Owen and Claire set out to find her, and eventually confront Lewis Dodgson, owner of Biosyn. Paleobotanist Ellie Sattler, Paleontologist Alan Grant, and Chaotician Ian Malcolm set out to expose Dodgson\'s schemes.</item>
        <item>Set 30 years after its predecessor, it follows Maverick\'s return to the United States Navy Strike Fighter Tactics Instructor program (also known as U.S. Navy-Fighter Weapons School - \"TOPGUN\"), where he must confront his past as he trains a group of younger pilots, among them the son of Maverick\'s deceased best friend Lieutenant Nick \"Goose\" Bradshaw, USN.</item>
        <item>Following the events of Spider-Man No Way Home, Doctor Strange unwittingly casts a forbidden spell that accidentally opens up the multiverse. With help from Wong and Scarlet Witch, Strange confronts various versions of himself as well as teaming up with the young America Chavez while traveling through various realities and working to restore reality as he knows it. Along the way, Strange and his allies realize they must take on a powerful new adversary who seeks to take over the multiverse.</item>
        <item>Follows the life of Father Stuart Long, a boxer-turned-priest who inspired countless people during his journey from self-destruction to redemption.</item>
        <item>Dangerously ill with a rare blood disorder, and determined to save others suffering his same fate, Dr. Morbius attempts a desperate gamble. What at first appears to be a radical success soon reveals itself to be a remedy potentially worse than the disease.</item>
        <item>Batman ventures into Gotham City\'s underworld when a sadistic killer leaves behind a trail of cryptic clues. As the evidence begins to lead closer to home and the scale of the perpetrator\'s plans become clear, he must forge new relationships, unmask the culprit and bring justice to the abuse of power and corruption that has long plagued the metropolis.</item>
        <item>Political activist Sofia is killed in an apparent hit-and-run accident outside of her home. Vietnam War veteran Travis Block works as a fixer for the Director of the FBI, Gabriel Robinson.Travis wants to retire and spend more time with his daughter and granddaughter. Mira, a journalist, claims to have information about Sofia\'s death and proof that it was not an accident. She got the intel from Dusty. Dusty also claims to have information about a top secret FBI operation called Project Unity, which kills innocent civilians like Sofia. Gabriel tells Travis that his last assignment is to bring in Dusty Crane. Travis has no choice now but to confront his FBI boss Gabriel with this information. Who is speaking the truth?</item>
        <item>In Moonfall, a mysterious force knocks the Moon from its orbit around Earth and sends it hurtling on a collision course with life as we know it. With mere weeks before impact and the world on the brink of annihilation, NASA executive and former astronaut Jo Fowler is convinced she has the key to saving us all - but only one astronaut from her past, Brian Harper and a conspiracy theorist K.C. Houseman believe her. These unlikely heroes will mount an impossible last-ditch mission into space, leaving behind everyone they love, only to find that they just might have prepared for the wrong mission.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>